Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Written Work, 24 Linear Feet in 23 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box.; 507 Megabytes in 6,369 digital files.
  - "Jerusalem", 1963; cuid35560 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - "Jerusalem: An Exercise", Undated; cuid35561 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - "Joel", Undated; cuid35562 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - "Journal", Undated; cuid35563 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - "Journal (Volume VIII)", 1975; cuid35564 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - "Juarez: The Digital Domain/The Bruise", 2004; cuid35565 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - "Judean Hills", Undated; cuid35566 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - "Just Gaming", Undated; cuid35567 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - "The Kantian Landscape", Undated; cuid35568 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - "Keene", Undated; cuid35569 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - "Kitty", Undated; cuid35570 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - "Knowledge Flux," Perforations 3, 1992; cuid35571 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - "Köld RaÞ Undan Hverju Rifi (Cold Counsels From Every Rib)", Undated; cuid35572 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - "Kudzu", Undated; cuid35573 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - "Kudzu," and Atlanta Writings, 1983-1984; cuid35574 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - "Landscape and Axiomatic", Undated; cuid35575 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - "Languor…", Undated; cuid35576 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - "Language and Structure", 1984; cuid35577 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - "Last Will and Testament", Undated; cuid35578 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - "Laura", Undated; cuid35579 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Laura Hayes "Breakthrough" 20 Minute Video Tape B/W, Undated; cuid35580 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - "Laurie Anderson: Procedure and Text", Undated; cuid35581 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - "Le Cinéma Sans Écran (Cinema Without the Screen)", 1980; cuid35582 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - "Left Hand, Right Hand", Undated; cuid35583 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - "Legwork", Undated; cuid35584 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - "Lesbian and Others Communities", Undated; cuid35585 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Letter From Rimbaud, from "Shortfilm" 1989, 20 Min., Undated; cuid35586 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - "Let Us Develop Literature and Art Suitable to the Encouragement of the Revolutionary Age", Undated; cuid35587 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - "The Lexicon as of August 10, 1989", cuid35588 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - "Lies", Undated; cuid35589 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - "The Life of Woman in Man, The Life of Man in Woman", 1974; cuid35590 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - "Life Support", Undated; cuid35591 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - "The Line Holds Business Well For Other Things", Undated; cuid35592 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - "Lineal and Nonlineal Codifications of Reality", Undated; cuid35593 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - "Lines (For Sitting Across the Table From Each Other)", Undated; cuid35594 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - "Liquid", Undated; cuid35595 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - "Lists", 1971; cuid35596 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - "Listening to A Side Joanless", Undated; cuid35597 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - "Literally Some Notes Towards the Work Surrounding Us", Undated; cuid35598 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Literary Agencies - Documents, Undated; cuid35599 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - "Literary Pastiche of No Consequence (Motley Pastiche)", Undated; cuid35600 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Literary Publishing - Documents, Undated; cuid35601 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - "Little Existentialist Poem", Undated; cuid35602 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - "Little German Poem", Undated; cuid35603 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - "Little Simple Romantic Poem: Country Fire", Undated; cuid35604 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - "Little Song", Undated; cuid35605 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - "The Location of the Mysteries", 1977; cuid35606 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - "Location or the Speaking Of It", 1978; cuid35607 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - "Locution", Undated; cuid35608 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - "The Logical Structure of Reality", Undated; cuid35609 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - "Logout/Fallout", Undated; cuid35610 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - "Loop/Loup", Undated; cuid35611 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - "Loop) or Without (Application of External Constraints)", Undated; cuid35612 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - "Los: A Magazine of Poetry", April, 1967; cuid35613 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - "Losing", Undated; cuid35614 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - "Lou Lou", Undated; cuid35615 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - "Love", Undated; cuid35616 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - "Love and the Beginning of Language: Ideograms of the Body", Undated; cuid35617 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - "Love and Writing", Undated; cuid35618 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - "Loved", Undated; cuid35619 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - "Lunchtime", Undated; cuid35620 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - "Madness", Undated; cuid35621 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - "The Mad Writings of a Displaced Person", Undated; cuid35622 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - "Mapping", Undated; cuid35623 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - "Mappings (Here)", Undated; cuid35624 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - "Manifesto", Undated; cuid35625 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - "The Man of Desire", 1983; cuid35626 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - "The Man Who Would Be Dog", Undated; cuid35627 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - "Marginalia (First Version, Indexical)", Undated; cuid35628 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - "Marginality", 1979; cuid35629 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Mathematical Writing, Undated; cuid35630 (Box 44, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - "Matrix", 1972 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - "Matter and Name", 1983; cuid35631 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - "Measurement and Substance", Undated; cuid35632 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "Memorial", Undated; cuid35633 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - "Memory", Undated; cuid35634 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - "Memory of Childhood Domesticity", Undated; cuid35635 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - "Memory of Painting, Undated; cuid35636 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - "Men Without Women", Undated; cuid35637 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - "Metabody", 1993-1997; cuid36130 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_10)
    "Metabody" is a hybrid CD-ROM/Website with multimedia components.
  - Meta, Ltd., Undated; cuid35638 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - "Metal Stories", Undated; cuid35639 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - "Metasaga", Undated; cuid35640 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - "Metastructure for Bricklaying", Undated; cuid35641 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - "Mexican", Undated; cuid35642 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - "Mexico", Undated; cuid35643 (Box 44, Folder 16, 17, 18, 19)
  - "Mindfuck", Undated; cuid35644 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - "Ministration", Undated; cuid35645 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - "Minox Piece", 1970; cuid35646 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - "Miscellaneous, Undated; cuid35647 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - "ML.TXT", Undated; cuid35648 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - "Model M", Undated; cuid35649 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - "Motherstructures", Undated; cuid35650 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - "Movie", Undated; cuid35651 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - "Movie Movie Movie", 1977; cuid35652 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - "Moving Inward: Rewrite of a Computer Language Generation Program", 1978-1979; cuid35653 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - "Mr. Jones Come Undone, Waiting in the Nightime Rain", Undated; cuid35654 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Muck, 2004; cuid35655 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - "My Future Work", Undated; cuid35656 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - "My Mouth Writing the Sucking of My Penis in This Heat My Writing, Undated; cuid35657 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - "Myth: Sources of Information", Undated; cuid35658 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - "My Theory", Undated; cuid35659 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - "Naivete", Undated; cuid35660 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Nancy Kitchell, 1967-1974; cuid35661 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - "The Narrows", Undated; cuid35662 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - "Nature and Discourse: 1975 Project", cuid35663 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - "Nature of the Theoretical", Undated; cuid35664 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - "Near-Death: In Jhaptal", Undated; cuid35665 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - "Negation", Undated; cuid35666 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - "Negative Culture: Some Notes", Undated; cuid35667 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - "The Neoconservative Left", Undated; cuid35668 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - "Neologisms" Website by mIEKAL aND, 2001; cuid36131 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_11)
  - "Newport Chunk", Undated; cuid35669 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - "News-Space", Undated; cuid35670 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - "Nicaragua", Undated; cuid35671 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - "Night -- On Saying Goodby to the Country", 1963; cuid35672 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - "Nightclub", Undated; cuid35673 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - "Nine Short Poems Influenced By the Spanish", Undated; cuid35674 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - "The Nixon Phenomenon", Undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - "Noche", Undated; cuid35675 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - "Noise Culture", Undated; cuid35676 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - "Noise Culture: Art and Society in the Third Millennium", 1992; cuid35677 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - "Noise Culture," Art Press, 1990; cuid35678 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - "The Noise of the Future: Crumbling Cities and Universal Dreams", Undated; cuid35679 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - "No Longer", Undated; cuid35680 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - "No Nietzsche's Eternal Recurrance: The Same Old Story", Undated; cuid35681 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - "Noosw w (The Poster Piece)", Undated; cuid35682 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - "North North Dallas Texas North", Undated; cuid35683 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - "No Sleep Empty Apartment Leaving, Suture, Cauterization…", 1982; cuid35684 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - "Notations", Undated; cuid35685 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - "Note on Assimilation Schema", 1972; cuid35686 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Notebook, Undated; cuid35687 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Notebooks, Undated; cuid35688 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - "The Notebook: Work on the Run from Fall 1977", cuid35689 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - "Notes for Talk", Undated; cuid35690 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - "Notes from the Sketchbook", Undated; cuid35691 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - "Notes on a Program for the Topology of Intention", Undated; cuid35692 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - "Notes on a Series of Videotapes Concerned with Positioning", Undated; cuid35693 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - "Notes on Business Hierarchies," Meta Ltd., Undated; cuid35694 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - "Notes on Coding and Symmetry", Undated; cuid35695 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - "Notes on Disaster (1972 Flood Wilkes-Barre/Kingston, Pennsylvania)," Meta Ltd., cuid35696 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - "Notes on Film", 1979; cuid35697 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - "Notes on Futurology", Undated; cuid35698 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - "Notes on International Unemployment", Undated; cuid35699 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - "Notes on Landscape", Undated; cuid35700 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - "Notes on Marx, Etc.", Undated; cuid35701 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Notes on Readings, Undated; cuid35702 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - "Notes on Reductivism, Etc.", Undated; cuid35703 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - "Notes on Set Theory", Undated; cuid35704 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Sondheim's Work, Undated; cuid35705 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - "Notes on the Mechanisms of Secrecy", Undated; cuid35706 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - "Notes on the Mode of Organism", Undated; cuid35707 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - "Notes Related to BCL Research", Undated; cuid35708 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - "Nothing but the Thing", Undated; cuid35709 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - "Novena", Undated; cuid35710 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - "Now I Write…", Undated; cuid35711 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - "Numbers", Undated; cuid35712 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - "Obligatory Disclaimers", Undated; cuid35713 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - "Occurrence, Event Situation", Undated; cuid35714 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - "Okay. That This is the One on Objects. That This is the One on Objects and Slipping. That This is on What Bothers Me.", Undated; cuid35715 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - "On a Discussion With Clark Coolidge", Undated; cuid35716 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - "On a Morning in Chicago", Undated; cuid35717 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - "On a Particular Mythic Conception", Undated; cuid35718 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - "On Assertion," Meta Ltd., Undated; cuid35719 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - "On Certain Remarkable Occurances", Undated; cuid35720 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - "On Drawing -- A Rhetoric", 1976; cuid35721 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - "One Speaks", Undated; cuid35722 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - "One Two", 1983; cuid35723 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - "On Her Leaving", Undated; cuid35724 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - "On Human Destructiveness", Undated; cuid35725 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - "On Inscription and Assertion in Relation to Relativized Null Sets", Undated; cuid35726 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - "On Machines", Undated; cuid35727 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - "On Painting", Undated; cuid35728 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - "On Quitting Music", Undated; cuid35729 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - "On Returning From Abroad: The Omens", Undated; cuid35730 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - "On Seeing the Longest Day", Undated; cuid35731 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - "On That Very Uncomfortable Edge: An Interview With Alan Sondheim," Arts Journal, 1989; cuid35732 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - "On the African Finger Piano," Brown Daily Herald, January 12 1966; cuid36113 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - "On the Error of Typing", 1984; cuid35733 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - "On the Inherent Transparency of the Material World", Undated; cuid35734 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - "On the Notebooks of Leonardo Da Vinci", Undated; cuid35735 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - "On the Phenomenology of Artificial Intelligence and Program Space", 1983; cuid35736 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - "On the Publication of Disorders of the Real, Undated; cuid35737 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - "On the Written in Relation to the Spoken", 1976; cuid35738 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - "On This Writing", Undated; cuid35739 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - "On Turbulence", Undated; cuid35740 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - "On Writing 'The Demolition of the Avant-Garde' ", Undated; cuid35741 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - "Opinions Give The Political Show Potence," The Atlanta Journal, June 24, 1984; cuid36108 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "Orange County California and the Economics of Language", Undated; cuid35742 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - "Or a Portrait", Undated; cuid35743 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - "Orders of the Real", 2005; cuid36132 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_12, Box 46, Folder 42)
  - "The Other Land", Undated; cuid35744 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - "The Others: Essays on the Imaginable", Undated; cuid35745 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - "Our Border Incident", Undated; cuid35746 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - "Our Own Border Incident", Undated; cuid35747 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - "The 'Our Experiment' ", Undated; cuid35748 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - "Outlaw Intellectualism: Natural Hermeneutics and Notes on Mechanisms of Secrecy I", 1977; cuid35749 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - "(Outline) Fabrication of a Culture: The Signature", Undated; cuid35750 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - "Over Arizona", Undated; cuid35751 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - "Paen", Undated; cuid35752 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - "Pain and Decadance - Dedicated to Huysmans", Undated; cuid35753 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - "The Painting", Undated; cuid35754 (Box 46, Folder 53, 54)
  - "(Painting ( or: ( or:: ( The Writing About Painting", Undated; cuid35755 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - "Painting A x B", Undated; cuid35756 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - "Parataxis", Undated; cuid35757 (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - "Part I. Time Symmetry and Acausality", Undated; cuid35758 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - "Part 3, The Fitfull Escapade", Undated; cuid35759 (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - "Partial Summarization/Ideology of the Media", Undated; cuid35760 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - "Part-Objects", Undated; cuid35761 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - "Party Fragment", Undated; cuid35762 (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - "Pathology", Undated; cuid35763 (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - "Penumbra/Grey", Undated; cuid35764 (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - "The Permanent Theses", Undated; cuid35765 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - "Pessimism", Undated; cuid35766 (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - "The Phenomenology and Function of Short-Wave," Ear Magazine, March 1984; cuid36112 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - "Phenomenology of the Bourgeois Home", Undated; cuid35767 (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - "Phenomenology of the Signature, Whiteman in the Mid-U.S.", 1978; cuid35768 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - "The Philosophy of Mystery", Undated; cuid35769 (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - "Philosophy" Web Narrative, 2006; cuid36133 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_13)
  - "The Photographs", Undated; cuid35770 (Box 47, Folder 1, 2)
  - "Photography", Undated; cuid35771 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - "Photography and Reality", Undated; cuid35772 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - "Photography, Angles and Mappings", Undated; cuid35773 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - "Photophobia", Undated; cuid35774 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - "The Physics and Psychology of Time", 1972; cuid35775 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - "Place-Names: Confessions of an Exile", 1989; cuid35776 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - "Plant", Undated; cuid35777 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - "Play 2", Undated; cuid35778 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - "Play 3", Undated; cuid35779 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - "Play Called Air", Undated; cuid35780 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - "Pleistocene", Undated; cuid35781 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - "PMS (Post-Modern Syndrome)", Undated; cuid35782 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - "Poem Hours", 1970; cuid35783 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - "Poem or 25", Undated; cuid35784 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - "Poem, Out, Line", 1969; cuid35785 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - "Poem to Susan", Undated; cuid35786 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - "The Poem Which Accompanies the Writing", Undated; cuid35787 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Poems by Charles Glass, Undated; cuid35788 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - "[Poetic Language: Linguistic Measure.]", 1971; cuid35789 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - "Point, Line, Cusp, Etc.", 1980; cuid35790 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Political Activism, Undated; cuid35791 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - "The Politics of Discourse/ Discourse of Politics", 1984; cuid35792 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - "Polymorphous Perverse Description", Undated; cuid35793 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - "Pornography, Its Penis, Its Vagina", 1981; cuid35794 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - "Portrayal", Undated; cuid35795 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - "Position Paper For Public Domain: Global Identity/Technology Project", Undated; cuid35796 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - "The Possibility of a Neutralizing Machine", Undated; cuid35797 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - " 'Postmodernist Aesthetics'-- Notes", Undated; cuid35798 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - "Potential of the Body", Undated; cuid35799 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - "Precis", Undated; cuid35800 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - "Premise", Undated; cuid35801 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - "The Presence of the Filmmaker, the Presence of the Film", Undated; cuid35802 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - "Presence of Future Presence of Video," Art Vu, 1994; cuid35803 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - "Presence: To Susan", Undated; cuid35804 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Press Coverage of Sondheim's Work, 1970-2008; cuid35805 (Box 47, Folder 37, 38, 39, 40)
  - "Presupposition of Non-Determination", Undated; cuid35806 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - "Prevarications", Undated; cuid35807 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - "The Principle of the Fragility of Good Things", Undated; cuid35808 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - "Principles of First Philosophy", 1991; cuid35809 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - "(Print)," Meta, Ltd., Undated; cuid35810 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - "Problematics of Noise", Undated; cuid35811 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - "Problème Posé Par Une Sculpture", 1972; cuid35812 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - "Proem", 1980; cuid35813 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - "Prolog", Undated; cuid35814 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - "Proof is in the Pudding", Undated; cuid35815 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - "Proposal for an Interactive Children's Program on Cable Television", 1976; cuid35816 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - "Proposal for Art Papers", Undated; cuid35817 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - "Psychology", Undated; cuid35818 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - "Psychosis", Undated; cuid35819 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Publication Sales, Undated; cuid35820 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Published Articles - Digital Copies and Drafts, 1999-2010; cuid36151 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_31)
    These files are digital copies and drafts of articles published in magazines and journals such as "Art papers" and "Millennium Film Journal."
  - Published Reviews - Digital Copies and Drafts, 2001-2010; cuid36152 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_32)
    These files include digital copies and drafts of published reviews. Alan Sondheim often reviewed books, films, electronics, and exhibits.
  - "Puzzle on Swallow Song I", Undated (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - "Quadrant Supervisor", Undated; cuid35821 (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - "The Qualms of Substance and Death", Undated; cuid35822 (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - "Quotations", Undated; cuid35823 (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - "Raise", Undated; cuid35824 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "Randy--", Undated; cuid35825 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - "Real Life Questions", Undated; cuid35826 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "Recognition of Entities", Undated; cuid35827 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - "Reel 3", Undated; cuid35828 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - "Relation of the Body", 1982; cuid35829 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - "The Relevance of Movement in Philosophy", Undated; cuid35830 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "Replacement Reading and the Seal of Approval", Undated; cuid35831 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - "Representation", Undated; cuid35832 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - "Representation of the Fundamental Rule", Undated; cuid35833 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - "The Representation of Women", Undated; cuid35834 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - "Reproduction Piece", Undated; cuid35835 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - "Rereading Disorders of the Real", Undated; cuid35836 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - "Resemblances and the Absent", Undated; cuid35837 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - "Resistance/Against the Text", Undated; cuid35838 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - "Resonances", 1971; cuid35839 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - "Review and Interview with Ravi Shankar," Brown Daily Herald, December 6 1967; cuid36118 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Reviews, Undated; cuid35840 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - "Rewhence", Undated; cuid35841 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - "Rewrite of Template Module", Undated; cuid35842 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - "Robbed Texts, Immobilization", 2000; cuid35843 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - "Rug 'Rug' Wall [ ]", 1969; cuid35844 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - "S--------grad", Undated; cuid35845 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - "S8," Image News, August 1987; cuid35846 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - "S.A. (Paysage)", Undated; cuid35847 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - "Sad Pastorale", Undated; cuid35848 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - "The Same", Undated; cuid35849 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - "Sampling Everyone", Undated; cuid35850 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - "San Francisco", Undated; cuid35851 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - "Scab/Coagulation/Clot", 1982; cuid35852 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - "Schemata of Transform Fine-Structures from the Fundamental Rule", 1977; cuid35853 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - "School of Fiction", Undated; cuid35854 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - "Science and Art: In Terms of Normal Activity.", Undated; cuid35855 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - "Sealing", Undated; cuid35856 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - "Seattle", Undated; cuid35857 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - "Second Gear", Undated; cuid35858 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - "Second Look", 1980; cuid35859 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - "Secret/code", Undated; cuid35860 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - "The Seen of it All", Undated; cuid35861 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - "Self/Ego/Simulacrum", Undated; cuid35862 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - "Self-Evident Points on Regionalism", Undated; cuid35863 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - "Self-Immersion", Undated; cuid35864 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - "Self-Indulgence", Undated; cuid35865 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - "Self-Portrait", Undated; cuid35866 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - "The Sensorium", 1984; cuid35867 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - "Sentencing/Death", 1985; cuid35868 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - "Separation, Beth", Undated; cuid35869 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - Sequence 3 (Sequence 1 and 2), Burning Deck, 1968; cuid35870 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - "Seri", Undated; cuid35871 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - "The Series Which Empties Itself of Place, But Extends by an Expansion of Air", Undated; cuid35872 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - "Serrated Edges", 1970; cuid35873 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - "Setting", Undated; cuid35874 (Box 49, Folder 1)